# Mikhail Makarov

trid364@gmail.com · t.me/raawrrrrrrrrrr Warsaw, Poland - EU resident

#### **SUMMARY**

Former legal professional with more than 4 years of various expertise with desire to build tech career. OPEN for hire, possibly for a trainee position

Inspiration to seek jobs in PC gamedev lies in my love both of classic titles and modern gems

Skills: process **mapping**, software **requirements** management, **modeling** techniques and tools, **document** management. Technical and in-app **writing** (copywriting). Strong verbal and written **communication**. Able to produce competent systemic **research**. Disciplined and well-managed

Languages: **English** - full professional proficiency; **Russian** and Belarusian - native

Technologies/tools: git, google workspace, miro, figma

Human rights advocate and call center volunteer

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### unrelated to dev

legal 2018-2022

2018-2022 - inhouse lawyer; attorney at law - full cycle of legal representation, including negotiation, complex legal research, developing of arguments, preparing and filing of lawsuits, presentation of cases before the judge in the oral hearing and following enforcement proceeding. As an attorney I was successful in a series of business and real-estate related projects, with court awards up to 500k \$

# related to dev

Mind-dev 2023 (Nov-Dec)

**Junior BA** - developing personal finance service (mobile and desktop app), responsible for technical and inapp (copy) writing, some of mobile app interface design, gathering and implementing software requirements, document management, manual QA

### **EDUCATION**

## **Belarusian State University**

2011-2018

Bachelors and consequently Master of laws (LLM) in business, contracts and banking

The reader of this CV has my consent to process my personal data included in this CV for the purposes of recruitment